[
  {
    "front": "Hi",
    "back": "안녕",
    "starred": false
  },
  {
    "front": "good",
    "back": "좋은",
    "starred": false
  },
  {
    "front": "impressed",
    "back": "감동적인",
    "starred": false
  },
  {
    "front": "bad",
    "back": "나쁜",
    "starred": false
  },
  {
    "front": "dangerous",
    "back": "위험한",
    "starred": false
  },
  {
    "front": "happy",
    "back": "행복한",
    "starred": false
  },
  {
    "front": "sad",
    "back": "슬픈",
    "starred": false
  },
  {
    "front": "interested",
    "back": "흥미로운",
    "starred": false
  },
  {
    "front": "bored",
    "back": "지루한",
    "starred": false
  },
  {
    "front": "foolish",
    "back": "바보같은",
    "starred": false
  },
  {
    "front": "slow",
    "back": "느린",
    "starred": false
  },
  {
    "front": "hard",
    "back": "어려운, 딱딱한",
    "starred": false
  },
  {
    "front": "easy",
    "back": "쉬운",
    "starred": false
  },
  {
    "front": "alive",
    "back": "살아있는",
    "starred": false
  },
  {
    "front": "safe",
    "back": "안전한",
    "starred": false
  },
  {
    "front": "sored",
    "back": "따끔거리는",
    "starred": false
  },
  {
    "front": "overestimated",
    "back": "과대평가된",
    "starred": false
  },
  {
    "front": "again",
    "back": "다시",
    "starred": false
  }
]